and we're going to go ahead and get
started. Ryan, throw us off or start us
off again.
>> Uh, hey Trey, first off, congratulations
and welcome to Las Vegas. My question
for you is you've you have experience
playing left tackle and center, but the
Raiders announced you as a guard. Uh,
how comfortably are you playing you
think you'll be playing guard in next
level and how much have the Raiders
talked to you during the pre-draft
process about the possibility of
switching to that position?
>> Right. Yeah, I'm comfortable playing all
five positions at the highest level. So,
I've got to play a bunch of guard in
practice and I'm ready to play it at the
highest level. So, whatever they need me
to play to get on the field is what I'm
going to play.
>> Trey, this is Hondo Carpenter. You're a
unique player in that you can literally
play all five spots. You're the SEC
offensive lineman of the year, but
you're so athletic. You fit perfectly
into Clint Kubak's system? I mean, is
there a better system more tailor made
to your skill set than what they do? And
can you talk about the privilege of
getting to play for the best offensive
line coach in the NFL and Rick Dennison?
>> Right. Yeah, I'm just so excited and so
honored to get to play for him and yeah,
there's not not a better system I could
play for that I could ask for. So, it's
just an honor to get to be a part of the
Raiders. So excited.
>> Hey, what do you what do you feel is
your best attribute or what do you feel
you bring uh to an NFL roster?
>> I think I bring my consistency and my
quick feet and you know, I'm a I'm a
smart player. I love to learn the
playbook and I love to learn about
football and have a high football IQ.
So, I'm going to learn the playbook as
soon as they get it out to me, and I'm
just going to be a consistent player and
get on the field as quick as I can.
>> Hey, Dre. Uh Sam Warren from The
Athletic. The Raiders obviously have the
number one overall pick, Tok Fernando
Mendoza. I'm wondering if you have any
familiarity with him and what you make
of the possibility of blocking for him.
>> I do not, but I am very excited to play
for play play for him and yeah, block
for him. You know, I can't wait and I
can't wait to meet him and I can't wait
to protect him back there. So, I'm just
excited.
>> Hey, Trey, obviously uh Clint Kubak did
a lot of the the zone reads or zone
running in his running game. Uh what do
you think of that kind of style uh and
approach to the running game and how
well do you think you'll fare in it
given your skill set and attributes?
>> I think I'm a perfect fit for that kind
of scheme and I just can't wait to get
going. So, yeah, I can't wait to prove
myself here coming up in rookie mini
camp and I can't wait to earn a spot.
Trey, Hondo Carpenter, again, when you
watch you play, you are a big man, but
you are down the field consistently.
There's there's run plays where you see
it 30 yards down the field. When you
talk about your stamina, it would appear
in watching you in third and fourth
quarters when you're 20 yards down the
field, your stamina is almost freakish.
Could you talk about that part of your
game as well, please?
>> Right. For sure. Yeah, I think that's a
super important thing to train because,
you know, picking up the running back
down the field or receiver or the ball
carrier, it's super important to me and
it was important to us at&m. So, that's
something I'll definitely continue uh as
being a Raider and I'll definitely yeah,
keep that as part of my game.
>> Hello.
>> Hi. Um, what does it mean to be on the
same page as a center, especially
someone like Tyler Linder Bomb?
Sorry, can you repeat that?
>> What does it mean to you to be on the
same page with a center, especially
someone like Tyler Linderbomb?
>> I mean, it means so much. It's going to
be such an honor, and I just can't wait
to meet him and get to get going.
>> Last one, Adam. Go ahead.
>> Just wondering, I mean, you grew up in
Fort Collins and went to Texas A&M. I
know Clint Kubak has ties to both
Colorado State and Texas A&M. Did you
have a familiarity with him at all uh
before this? And I guess how much did
you talk to the Raiders throughout this
process?
>> I did not have a ton of famili
familiarity before the process, but
yeah, I got to talk with them quite a
bit throughout the process and I'm just
excited to get going. You know, can't
really just can't wait to get there and
get started.
>> Is is that Sorry. Is that is that a team
that you thought
uh there was a possibility was going to
take you based on your interactions?
>> Yes, sir. Definitely.
>> Cool.
>> Great. All right. Thanks so much, Trey.
Really appreciate you.
>> Yep. Thank you. Thanks everybody.